<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mike&#39;s Code</title>
    <link>https://zenrix.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mike&#39;s Code</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Micheal Earl</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zenrix.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Godot</title>
      <link>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2019-06-05-godot-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2019-06-05-godot-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Godot is a lot of fun to use and, in my opinion, may be the best platform available for teaching people how to program. Godot is very lightweight (~50mb) with no dependencies, it is completely open source under the MIT License, it supports both 2d and 3d game development, and its scripting language is python-esque.
I think all of those things are excellent reasons for beginners to use Godot. However, that isn&amp;rsquo;t to say Godot doesn&amp;rsquo;t suit advanced programmers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Bad at This</title>
      <link>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2019-06-04-bad-at-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2019-06-04-bad-at-this/</guid>
      <description>Wow it just never really seems to work out every time I try to get this blog going. I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest here: I usually just forget it exists. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to say to myself &amp;ldquo;Oh I can wait to make another blog post.&amp;rdquo; And, I&amp;rsquo;ll keep telling myself that right up until I completely forget about the blog entirely.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be going back and doing some editing (some of my posts sorely require it) and maybe this time I can actually stick with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2018-08-02-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2018-08-02-home/</guid>
      <description>I just got back home from my trip to Canada. I had a lot of fun during the trip, but I am glad to be back home so I can start getting some work done. My next semester of college begins in only two weeks, and most of the classes are still general education.
Making sure that I&amp;rsquo;m always learning something new about technology is a must. Becoming complacent would be very bad at this step in my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decisions</title>
      <link>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2018-07-15-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2018-07-15-decisions/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what to do. My knowledge is all over the place. I can tell you a little bit about basically any web stack or language, but not enough to show true proficiency or capability. It is time to change my habits and really stick to something. I just have no idea what that something should be.
My real goal is to be a game developer. I want to make games from the ground up through code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escaping Lua</title>
      <link>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2018-07-09-escaping-lua/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2018-07-09-escaping-lua/</guid>
      <description>I love Lua as a programming language. It really has mostly everything I would ever want from a programming language. It is speedy (using LuaJIT) and it is easy to pick up. Using Lua and LÖVE for projects is a joy.
However, I have never been a very big fan of Lua syntax. It seems a really shallow thing to be upset with considering how good everything else seems to be, but I just can&amp;rsquo;t escape how strange it can be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nostalgia</title>
      <link>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2018-07-08-nostalgia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2018-07-08-nostalgia/</guid>
      <description>Writing has always been a difficult beast for me. Every time I sit down to write something, I just fail to bring anything substantial to mind. I don&amp;rsquo;t live a fanciful life of tantalizing adventure but, rather, a fanciful life of mediocre preservation.
Every time I come back to trying to write on my blog, my eyes are drawn to my first post: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m still alive&amp;rdquo;. Ironic, because that is not actually my first post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rust and C</title>
      <link>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2018-08-05-rust-and-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2018-08-05-rust-and-c/</guid>
      <description>I made a post a while back about how I need to pick something and really go at it for a while. Finally, I have come to a decision regarding that post. My focus from this point will be on systems level programming (with some web).
C has always been really fun for me. I like having powerful low level control, but I&amp;rsquo;m less thrilled about all the pitfalls that I encounter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Object Oriented Lua</title>
      <link>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2018-03-03-been-a-while/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2018-03-03-been-a-while/</guid>
      <description>Well this blog didn&amp;rsquo;t really take off. I just can&amp;rsquo;t spin up the effort to write something every day. I&amp;rsquo;ve recently gotten into Lua and the LOVE 2d game library. Playing around with that has been pretty fun.
I&amp;rsquo;m using a library in lua to help me implement OOP functionality. The library is called classical.lua and you can find it here.
You can see some notes I made on the usage of the classical library in my repo here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Alive</title>
      <link>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2016-01-20-im-alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zenrix.github.io/posts/2016-01-20-im-alive/</guid>
      <description>Sorry I haven&amp;rsquo;t been very active these past few weeks. I&amp;rsquo;ve been preparing myself to move back to the city. I&amp;rsquo;ll finally have a decent internet connection again! I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to getting all this moving stuff over with.
I originally wanted to write a post about event handlers in C#, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been too distracted. This is going to be a pretty short post.
I will be writing new posts in the future, so if anyone is actually reading this you can expect some content in the next week or so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>https://zenrix.github.io/pages/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zenrix.github.io/pages/archive/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://zenrix.github.io/pages/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zenrix.github.io/pages/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>Work in progress! In the mean time, why not check out some of my Github projects?
 https://github.com/Zenrix/bytelo Top down 2D shooter made with Lua and LOVE
https://github.com/Zenrix/roque Framework for making roguelike games on the web
https://github.com/Zenrix/r-lyke A tiny roguelike written in Ruby</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://zenrix.github.io/pages/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zenrix.github.io/pages/resume/</guid>
      <description>Micheal Earl Arcata, California, United States michealearldev@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/micheal-earl  Summary I am driven to learn new technologies and deep dive into what makes them tick. I have 2 years of web development experience, a decade of tinkering under my belt, and I am proficient in all areas of web development with a focus on the back end. I have used many ORM&amp;rsquo;s, databases, and server languages. My preferences are Node.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
